apliiq.com 2013-11-14

# Privacy Policy

privacy policy - apliiq - custom test

Thanks for using [http://www.apliiq.com](http://www.apliiq.com/) (the "Apliiq Website"). At Apliiq Inc. ("Apliiq"), we are committed to protecting your privacy. We have created this privacy policy to make sure you know what information we collect and how we use it. By using our the Apliiq Website you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy. From time to time, we may update this privacy policy. We encourage you to check back and review this privacy policy so that you always will know what personally identifiable information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the Apliiq Website will be subject to the then current privacy policy. ****

****

**  
But first, a note about uploading and posting information on the Apliiq Website:**

At the time you register for an Apliiq account, you will choose and provide us with your email, first name, last name and password. When you save or share a design, post a description, comment, image or video on the Apliiq Website, your name, Content and Design are visible to other users. Additionally, if your comment or message contains personal information and is posted by you in a page that is accessible to the public, third parties may make note of the information and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties as a result. Any content or information you upload is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. Always use care when you post such information. ****

**

What information do we collect? 

**

****Information Provided by You:

You may provide us with certain personally identifiable information when you: 

  * register for an Apliiq account; 
  * order products or gift certificates; 
  * request customer support or send us any other communication; 
  * sign up for newsletters, email alerts, and special offers; 
  * set up a Seller account; 
  * enter sweepstakes or contests; 
  * sign up for, or redeem, special offers; 
  * respond to surveys; 
  * use our Email-to-a-Friend 
  * approve your child's request to open an Apliiq account in accordance with The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). 

Such information may include your name, email address, billing address, shipping address, Paypal billing information, and credit card number. You may also provide us with information about other people, such as their email addresses, if you email a product to a friend or refer a friend to the Apliiq Website or our promotions. 

Information Collected by Cookies:

Apliiq uses cookies on the Apliiq Website. A cookie is a small text file on your computer which a website sends to your computer to allow the website to store information which uniquely identifies our users. Apliiq's cookies do not collect or store personally identifiable information. Rather, the cookie stores a token which uniquely identifies a particular user. That token is then linked to the user information in our secured databases. You can always reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to display a message when a cookie is being sent. If you reset your browser, some of the Apliiq Website features and functionality such as personalization of information may not be available to you. 

Information Collected by Web Beacons and Log Files:

Apliiq collects certain non-personally identifiable information through the use of web beacons and log files. Such information may include your IP address, browser type, site usage, and whether you opened emails you received from us. ****

****

**  
How do we secure your information?**

When you place orders or access your account information, we use commercially reasonable and generally-accepted technological safeguards to secure any information we collect about you. The secure server software (SSL) Apliiq uses encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. In addition, your Apliiq account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. You should always take steps to protect the confidentiality of the password you select. 

We operate internationally and many of our computer systems are currently based in the United States. As a result, your personal data will be processed by Apliiq in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create a user account with us, you agree to this privacy policy and you consent to the transfer of all information you provide to the United States. ****

****

**  
How do we use information?**

We use the personally identifiable information you provide to: 

  * provide the features and functionality of the Apliiq Website; 
  * fulfill your requests for our products and services; 
  * pay commissions and referral fees; 
  * communicate with you about the status of your orders and other inquiries about our products and services; 
  * send you information about our products and services with your permission; and 
  * provide notices about the results of sweepstakes, contest, and other promotions. 

We use your email address to communicate with you about your account and to send you certain notification emails.

We use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send marketing messages and notifications from time-to-time. You may unsubscribe to email notifications communications by clicking 

We use non-personally identifiable information to monitor the use and performance of the Apliiq Website so that we can learn more about how people use the Apliiq Website and improve our products and services. ****

****

**  
Does Apliiq disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**

Generally, Apliiq does not share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your consent except that: 

Apliiq provides information to its agents and trusted service providers and contractors for limited purposes, such as: fulfilling customer orders and processing credit card transactions; offering certain products and services; communicating with customers; providing customer service; managing information on our behalf; and enhancing the Apliiq Website features and functionality. In such cases, we require that these parties agree to use the information solely for the purpose for which we provided it to them and in accordance with our privacy policy. 

If you sign up for a promotion (e.g., a contest or sweepstakes offer) or enroll in a service we offer in partnership with a third party, we may provide information with your permission (such as your name, email address, and account activity) to such third parties. 

From time-to-time, Apliiq may provide its sellers with the first name and city/state/country of residence of Apliiq customers who have purchased such seller's products. 

Apliiq may also release information (including your name, addresses, telephone number, and account activity) when we, in our sole discretion believe that such release is necessary or appropriate to: 

  * comply with law; 
  * comply with subpoenas, warrants, court orders, government investigations, or other legal process; 
  * enforce or apply the terms of any of our user or license agreements; 

  * investigate or respond to allegations of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other unlawful activity 

  * investigate fraud or similar claims 

  * protect the rights, property or safety of Apliiq, our users, or others. 

In the event that Apliiq is acquired by, or merged with, another company Apliiq reserves the right to transfer all information we have collected from our users in connection with such acquisition or merger and to inform the new owner of the privacy policy in place at the time the information was given. 

Apliiq may disclose non-personally-identifiable information to third parties in aggregate form to potential business partners and investors. ****

** **

**  
What about Children's Privacy?**

Children under the age of 13 are allowed to upload graphics and images and to order products with their parent's consent. To order products, the child must submit his or her name and his or her mailing address and shipping address if different from the mailing address together with a valid credit card number. This is the only information collected from a child. 

This information is used to fulfill the requested order; confirm shipment; complete record keeping including commissions entitlements and pay commissions fees, and to advise the child concerning new Apliiq products, services or policies. 

Parents of children under the age of 13 have the option to consent to the collection of this information from their children or not. Such consent will not be used as consent for the dissemination of any of this information and the information will not be released by Apliiq to third parties without the parents' consent except as may be required by law or upon court order or as specified in our Privacy Policy. 

Personal information at Apliiq is kept confidential and is disclosed only with the consent of the Apliiq user or as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We do not engage in the selling of the habits, behavior, buying patterns, or demographic information of our users. Apliiq does not condition a child's participation in any on-line activity on the granting of any unnecessary information beyond that actually needed in connection with that activity. 

Parents can review any information Apliiq has received from a child and the parent can have that information deleted and the parent can forbid the collection of additional information from their child. If you want to review any information obtained from your child or if you want to have any information obtained from your child deleted from the Apliiq records or to forbid any use of such information, you may send a request to Apliiq Customer Support by emailing cs@apliiq.com. Alternatively, you may contact the Apliiq Child Privacy Representative by phone, email, or letter at: 

Apliiq Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
440 Seaton St. #207  
Los Angeles, CA 90013  
cs@apliiq.com  
213 253 2727  
**  
**

**How can I change, delete, or update my information?**

Most of your account information can be changed in the My Account Details in the My Apliiq section of the Apliiq Website. The current version of the Apliiq Privacy Policy was adopted effective as of 8/01/2011. 

****

created with love in Los Angeles 

* * *

## experience fabric expression

It's one of the basic necessities of life, we need it to stay warm and cover our privates, but it so often goes unnoticed, overlooked in a sea of mass produced trends.

Envision a world where fabric tells a story, where it means something special because you chose it, it's your style, it's unique. Join us in making fabric a platform for creativity and expression, revolutionizing consumption one patch at a time. Own what you wear, and be you.

Use of this web site constitutes acceptance of the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy. Copyright © 2009-2012, Apliiq Inc. All rights reserved.
